<chat>

	<welcome>
	
		<greeting id="1" style="neutral">Hello</greeting>
		<greeting id="2" style="friendly">Hi</greeting>
		<greeting id="3" style="friendly">How're you diddlin'?</greeting>
		<greeting id="4" style="friendly">Aye up</greeting>
		<greeting id="5" style="neutral">Now then</greeting>
		<greeting id="6" style="neutral">Good day</greeting>
		<greeting id="7" style="neutral">Greetings</greeting>
		<greeting id="8" style="rude">...</greeting>
		<greeting id="9" style="friendly">G'day</greeting>
		<greeting id="10" style="friendly">Wassup</greeting>
		<greeting id="11" style="neutral">Hey there</greeting>
		<greeting id="12" style="neutral">Easy dude</greeting>
	
	</welcome>
	
	<conversation id="1" style="rude">
	
		<step number="1">I don't have time for this nonsense. Can't you ask someone else???</step>
		<step number="2">OK, i'll tell you this...I wouldn't trust the man in the suit. He talks out of the wrong end most of the time...</step>
		<step number="3">Insistent, aren't we? Fine. Go check out number ##. People like to tell tall tales about the shenanigans that go on at that place.</step>
		<step number="4">But I don't really care!</step>
	
	</conversation>
	
	<conversation id="2" style="neutral">
	
		<step number="1">Oh, I don't really know. I don't live here, see.</step>
		<step number="2">All I can do is pass on what my friend told me.</step>
		<step number="3">Her at number ## is a diagnosed kleptomaniac...and you don't want to know where she stashes certain things.</step>
		<step number="4">Anyway, i'm not one to gossip.</step>
	
	</conversation>
	
	<conversation id="3" style="friendly">
	
		<step number="1">Oh yes. I know where you can find it. For sure.</step>
		<step number="2">I always have my ear on the grapevine. Knowledge is power in these parts.</step>
		<step number="3">You have got to make sure that you know everyone else's business. You never know when it could come in handy.</step>
		<step number="4">Sorry, I digress. I would go knock on number ##'s door if I were you.</step>
	
	</conversation>
	
	<conversation number="4" style="neutral">
	
		<step number="1">You're looking for what? I can't say that i've ever heard of it.</step>
		<step number="2">I wouldn't even know where to start looking.</step>
		<step number="3">The guy in the suit? He looks like a knowledgable fellow. You should go ask him.</step>
		<step number="4">If I had to make a wild guess, i'd say the guy at number ## has something to hide. Always looks a bit shifty that one.</step>
		
	</conversation>
	
	<conversation number="5" style="rude">
	
		<step number="1">O.M.G, you're like, such a shallow person!</step>
		<step number="2">You should look past such insignificant things. Then maybe you could find your own path towards enlightenment.</step>
		<step number="3">Come, meditate with me...no? Oh, ok then. I guess not everybody is ready to rid themselves of ego and be at peace with everyone, and the world around them!</step>
		<step number="4">I'm not one to judge though. But, if you insist on finding it, you could do worse than ring the bell on number ##. She is such a slut.</step>
	
	</conversation>

</chat>